We are the best
天选至强
Angels of fire
烈焰天使
Divine divine divine
神圣无上
We fell from the sky with halos of gold
携金色光环自苍穹降临
Wings of the light we rise never grow old
展光之羽翼永葆青春
Shining so bright we're more than a dream
璀璨辉光超越梦境
The world can't hold us we're heaven's supreme
天地难拘我辈天界至尊
We guide the way
指引前路
Through darkest night
穿越至暗之夜
We are the best from heaven sent
吾等天选至强
Crowned in light, forever blessed.
圣光加冕 永承天恩
Above the rest, we soar and shine,
凌驾众生 翱翔闪耀
Angels of fire, divine, divine divine
烈焰天使 神圣无上
Divine divine divine
神圣无上
Divine divine
We rise like the dawn, with strength in our soul,
如破晓腾跃 魂蕴伟力
Fearless and free, we're reaching our goal.
无畏无拘 直抵宏图
Glowing with power, we'll never back down,
神力辉耀 永不退缩
Kings of the skies, we wear the crown.
苍穹之王 冠冕在握
We guide the way,
指引前路
Through darkest night.
穿越至暗之夜
We are the best, from heaven sent,
吾等天选至强
Crowned in light, forever blessed.
圣光加冕 永承天恩
Above the rest, we soar and shine,
凌驾众生 翱翔闪耀
Angels of fire, divine, divine divine
烈焰天使 神圣 神圣无上
Divine divine divine
神圣无上
With hearts of fire, we light the way,
炽心燃焰 照彻征途
The way
征途
Nobody stops us, we're here to stay.
无人可阻 永恒屹立
Here to stay
永恒屹立
Together we stand, we're bold, we're strong,
同心而立 无畏刚强
We're strong
刚强
Fans and the angels, where we belong.
粉丝与天使 归心之所
Through darkest night.
穿越至暗之夜
We are the kings, from heaven sent,
吾等天选君王
Crowned in light, forever blessed.
圣光加冕 永承天恩
Above the rest, we soar and shine,
凌驾众生 翱翔闪耀
Angels of fire, divine, divine
烈焰天使 神圣 神圣
We are the best. Heaven sent
吾等至强 天选而降
We are the best, from heaven sent
吾等天选至强
Crowned in light, forever blessed.
圣光加冕 永承天恩
Forever blessed.
永承天恩
Above the rest, we soar and shine
凌驾众生 翱翔闪耀
Soar and shine
翱翔闪耀
Angels of fire, divine, divine divine
烈焰天使 神圣无上